<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>ryan.c</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on ryan.c</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Apr 2018 12:24:17 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Publishing a Decentralized Blog</title>
      <link>/blog/getting-started/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Apr 2018 12:24:17 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/getting-started/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The promising aspect of Beaker is that all web technologies work as expected. The fact that visting a site is as simple as creating an &lt;code&gt;index.html&lt;/code&gt; and placing &lt;code&gt;dat&lt;/code&gt; instead of &lt;code&gt;http&lt;/code&gt; in front of the URL is a great start. The trickier aspect is teaching yourself to think in terms of a static, shared infrastructure instead of a central one. No database means that a static CMS is needed to manage the blog.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Decentralized Web : First Impressions</title>
      <link>/blog/first-impressions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2018 15:17:53 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/first-impressions/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;After reading &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.oreilly.com/ideas/its-time-to-rebuild-the-web&#34;&gt;Time to Rebuild the Web?&lt;/a&gt; and the &lt;a href=&#34;(https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=16847781)&#34;&gt;accompanying Hacker News discussion&lt;/a&gt;, I felt compelled to jump in and give &lt;a href=&#34;https://beakerbrowser.com/&#34;&gt;Beaker&lt;/a&gt; a shot. I was instantly excited. They type of excited where eight hours fly by and you don&amp;rsquo;t want to leave your computer. That said, I&amp;rsquo;m not sure if the appeal was from nostalgia or innovation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A small project example : add yours !</title>
      <link>/projects/shuffled/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/shuffled/</guid>
      <description>Along with Ford Prefect, Dent barely escapes the Earth&amp;rsquo;s destruction as it is demolished to make way for a hyperspace bypass. Arthur spends the next several years, still wearing his dressing gown, helplessly launched from crisis to crisis while trying to straighten out his lifestyle.
 He rather enjoys tea, but seems to have trouble obtaining it in the far reaches of the galaxy.
 In time, he learns how to fly and carves a niche for himself as a sandwich-maker.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>/projects/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2015 20:29:37 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/projects/</guid>
      <description>In this theme, it is possible to add sections like a Projects one for example. You can add plenty of articles about your projects and a presentation page that will be displayed before the list. All is modulable, if you don&amp;rsquo;t want something.
A Hollywood-funded film version, produced and filmed in the UK, was released in April 2005, and radio adaptations of the third, fourth, and fifth novels were broadcast from 2004 to 2005.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/contact/</guid>
      <description>Reach me</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Home</title>
      <link>/home/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/home/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m a husband, father, developer, gamer, runner and lots of other er&amp;rsquo;s. I finish some projects and attempt to finish others.
I believe writing is a hobby with benefits, so I share my thoughts here.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>