<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog Section on ryan.c</title>
    <link>https://ryancampbell.blog/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blog Section on ryan.c</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 07 May 2018 20:06:53 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://ryancampbell.blog/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Add Jazzy Docs to Hugo</title>
      <link>https://ryancampbell.blog/blog/add-jazzy-docs-to-hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 May 2018 20:06:53 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ryancampbell.blog/blog/add-jazzy-docs-to-hugo/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m still riding this wave of excitement for static sites and free hosting, so the next step for me was to build my code documentation right into my Hugo sites instead of a separate standalone instance on Github Pages.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Responsive Design With Moom</title>
      <link>https://ryancampbell.blog/blog/responsive-design-with-moom/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 May 2018 06:58:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ryancampbell.blog/blog/responsive-design-with-moom/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Responsive design is not meant to be about the device. It&amp;rsquo;s about the breakpoints that your design needs, and supporting them correctly. That&amp;rsquo;s why when dragging the browser to resize your site, the design should look good at all widths. And even though that&amp;rsquo;s true, I still have a desire to verify how the design would look on a specific device like a portrait iPad.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Automating Workspaces on macOS</title>
      <link>https://ryancampbell.blog/blog/automating-workspaces-on-macos/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 May 2018 00:21:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ryancampbell.blog/blog/automating-workspaces-on-macos/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I now have 4 side projects in motion along with personal tasks like finance and communication. For the first time, my go to workspace solution of mission control and spaces doesn&amp;rsquo;t cut it. Between Xcode, multiple terminal windows running, Photoshop, Mail, Photos, Sketch, and so on I finally felt overwhelmed. It&amp;rsquo;s time for a new solution.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Lot Changes in Five Years</title>
      <link>https://ryancampbell.blog/blog/a-lot-changes-in-six-years/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Apr 2018 19:29:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ryancampbell.blog/blog/a-lot-changes-in-six-years/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I recently offered to create a website for a local charity, and then it hit me &amp;ndash; I haven&amp;rsquo;t made a website in five years. Sure, I made this site and got on the &lt;a href=&#34;http://ryancampbell.blog/blog/i-m-late-to-the-jamstack-party/&#34;&gt;decentralized bandwagon&lt;/a&gt;, but I haven&amp;rsquo;t done something from scratch in some time. Especially on the design and responsive front. Now that I&amp;rsquo;m finished, I thought it may be useful to share my notes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I&#39;m Late to the JAMStack Party</title>
      <link>https://ryancampbell.blog/blog/i-m-late-to-the-jamstack-party/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Apr 2018 17:29:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ryancampbell.blog/blog/i-m-late-to-the-jamstack-party/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It turns out my new found &lt;a href=&#34;http://ryancampbell.blog/blog/getting-started/&#34;&gt;fascination with decentralized websites&lt;/a&gt; isn&amp;rsquo;t specific to them being decentralized. The movement of static sites has a place on the current web too &amp;ndash; &lt;a href=&#34;https://jamstack.org&#34;&gt;JAMStack&lt;/a&gt;. For the past year people have been researching ways to take away the traditional centralized back end, and it&amp;rsquo;s pretty neat.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adding a Codepen Shortcode to Hugo</title>
      <link>https://ryancampbell.blog/blog/codepen-shortcode/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Apr 2018 12:36:17 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ryancampbell.blog/blog/codepen-shortcode/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Shortcodes allow you to add external content to a blog post in a user friendly way. Someone&amp;rsquo;s tweet, an instagram photo, forms, and so on. Instead of a long ugly snippet of JavaScript, you can paste one line of clean shortcode. Hugo has &lt;a href=&#34;https://gohugo.io/content-management/shortcodes/&#34;&gt;built in shortcode support&lt;/a&gt;, and adding a custom shortcode is super easy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Forestry &#43; Hugo &#43; Netlify</title>
      <link>https://ryancampbell.blog/blog/forestry---hugo---netlify/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Apr 2018 01:17:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ryancampbell.blog/blog/forestry---hugo---netlify/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Just when I thought my publishing setup was finalized, I stumbled across &lt;a href=&#34;https://forestry.io&#34;&gt;Forestry&lt;/a&gt;. Forestry appears to solve my GUI wishlist all at once. GUI for Hugo? Check. Well designed for clients? Check. Can be mapped to my URL? Check. Well supported and documented? Check.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publishing a Decentralized Blog</title>
      <link>https://ryancampbell.blog/blog/getting-started/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Apr 2018 12:24:17 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ryancampbell.blog/blog/getting-started/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The promising aspect of Beaker is that all web technologies work as expected. The fact that visting a site is as simple as creating an &lt;code&gt;index.html&lt;/code&gt; and placing &lt;code&gt;dat&lt;/code&gt; instead of &lt;code&gt;http&lt;/code&gt; in front of the URL is a great start. The trickier aspect is teaching yourself to think in terms of a static, shared infrastructure instead of a central one. No database means that a static CMS is needed to manage the blog.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Decentralized Web : First Impressions</title>
      <link>https://ryancampbell.blog/blog/first-impressions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2018 15:17:53 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ryancampbell.blog/blog/first-impressions/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;After reading &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.oreilly.com/ideas/its-time-to-rebuild-the-web&#34;&gt;Time to Rebuild the Web?&lt;/a&gt; and the &lt;a href=&#34;(https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=16847781)&#34;&gt;accompanying Hacker News discussion&lt;/a&gt;, I felt compelled to jump in and give &lt;a href=&#34;https://beakerbrowser.com/&#34;&gt;Beaker&lt;/a&gt; a shot. I was instantly excited. They type of excited where eight hours fly by and you don&amp;rsquo;t want to leave your computer. That said, I&amp;rsquo;m not sure if the appeal was from nostalgia or innovation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>